How we doing?
>> How you guys doing? How you guys doing?
>> Doing freaking awesome.
>> Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Man, thank you, man.
Thank you.
>> One of you guys, just how excited are
you to be here? I know yesterday.
>> Yeah. You know, I mean, like it just,
you know, um a blessing, honestly. Um,
it it just, you know, a dream come true,
honestly. Uh, and when, you know,
and when I heard my name call, you know,
uh, it was just, you know, um,
excitement.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm so excited. I mean, I feel
like, you know, just got to be honest,
one of my first thoughts was I don't get
to I don't have to play Miles Garrett on
Sundays. So, that's uh something to be
excited about in itself. But I mean,
just to be here, um, to be here, be with
these teammates, to be able to, um, play
for these fans, it's it's an honor.
>> To follow up on that, I mean, left come
through here before and talk about going
up against Miles and that challenge that
it is. How much are you looking forward
to getting that opportunity in training
camp practices even?
>> I am so excited. I mean, I feel like
there's no way there's no better way for
me to get better. then going against
someone like that. I mean, just maybe
the best player in the world. So, um to
go against him every day is going to be
a blessing.
>> Both of you guys, you've talked about
versatility, you know, positional
versatility. How much more important is
that becoming in football that you know,
you're not just a left tackle or a right
tackle or an outside receiver. How much
more important do you feel like it's
it's becoming in the game?
Yeah, you know, um you know, uh it's
much more important now. Um you know, um
the more things you can do, um the
better your value is. Um the faster you
learn, um the more plays you get. Um,
you know, uh, just, you know, just, you
know, being able just, you know, being
just, you know, being able to play, just
being able to play, you know, all across
the field, you know, um, is just going
to, you know, open up, you know, uh,
many more opportunities.
>> Yeah, man. It's And you never know
what's going to happen on the football
field. Like, someone could go down. Um,
I think it's it's a good thing to be
able to fill in wherever I need to. Um,
yeah, it's it's it's a big thing. And
then not only that, is that knowing how
to play uh multiple different positions
just broadens or
I don't know, it it broadens your
knowledge on the game itself um on how
every play works. So, I feel like
there's nothing but positives that come
with knowing multiple positions.
>> You were probably uh playing when games
and Shador Sanders was playing,
>> but have you had a chance to to watch
him play and what will it be like to
catch?
>> Yes, sir. So, um I actually got, you
know, um kind of like story. Um so,
whenever I had entered the transfer
portal, um my uh after my sophomore
season, um I had actually went down to
Colorado and you know, um you know, uh
and met Shadur um you know, um he's you
know, um a great guy, a great leader. Um
I just you know I just I just cannot you
know build that you know relationship
build that you know and and build that
you know um
connection with them.
>> What was it like for you to hear Andrew
Barry say to you on the phone yesterday
during your draft call uh that they
expect you to be their left tackle their
franchise left of the future? I mean,
shoot, I'm ready or I feel like it's it
was such it's such a cool thing to be
believed in and I'm not one that likes
to let people down. So,
>> Andrew told us not to be fooled by your
personality. I think you said don't be
fooled by your kindness. Is there a
switch that just flips with you when you
step on the field?
>> Um,
I I guess you could say that. I guess
you could say that. I don't know.
There's just something about I don't
know. There's something about just
ah I don't know that's a little corny.
So let me think of something else.
All right. But it's like the same thing
saying there's no greater joy of moving
a man from point A to point B against
his will. There's really nothing like
it. You know when you're just pushing a
guy back he's like swinging at your
arms. Like there's no feeling like that.
And then to be able to put someone in
the dirt that's it's awesome.
>> Talked about Thomas a little bit
yesterday. Um, first of all, his he
reached out to you yet since you've been
drafted?
>> Uh, no. No. But
>> what drew you to him when you growing up
watching left tackles and what stood out
about his game where you just called him
the best of all time?
>> Well, I mean, I feel like a big thing
about him is this that I saw. I feel
it's a really big character thing, too,
is the fact that he played 10 years and
didn't miss a snap. I feel like that was
like the biggest thing at first where it
was like I think that's insane because
there's you there's you know there's no
way that he got through 10 seasons
healthy and the fact that he never
missed a snap. Um I think that just as
like a when I was younger too showed me
like his character um and how well he
played those 10 seasons too or his whole
career. Um to me it's it's kind of
undeniable of all time.
reading that letter you wrote to to GM
and you called yourself you said you're
the best receiver in the draft class. I
guess what makes you say that? What
gives you that confidence to say that?
>> Um like I said before, you know, um you
know, um I'm very confident. Um I feel
like, you know, um I I feel like, you
know, I am the, you know, I feel like I
am the most versatile. I feel like um I
feel like I feel like I am the I feel
like I feel like I am the best you know
playmaker you know um you know you know
um about a group but you know uh
everybody you know um is amazing you
know um everybody you know um you know
uh everybody has you know everybody has
their you know um
everybody has things you know that um
everybody has their things that you know
that everybody does well. So,
>> just address the fact that Andrew Barry
when he talked to us, he told us that
after he read your letter, he actually
picked up the phone and called you to
tell you uh just how much that moved
him. Uh what did it mean to you to hear
from him in those words when you weren't
even sure if you were going to be here
or not? And, you know, how did you feel
about that?
>> You know, uh it meant a lot. um you you
know um just you know having him you
know um read the letter you know um you
know um you know him you know um and him
you know reaching out you know um and
showing love and support
uh you know this obviously you're taking
in the experience of being drafted by a
team if you'll do that but how eager are
you for the next step of getting to work
on these practice fields and taking part
of rookie mini camp and really getting
to fit into this organ organization.
>> Yeah, I'm just I'm excited to because I
know there's going to be a learning
curve. I mean, I'm going against dudes
that are bigger, faster, stronger than
guys I've ever gone against. So, I'm
excited to um to be able to take that
challenge head on and just get better.
>> Yeah. Um honestly, you know, uh I'm just
ready to work also. Um I'm ready to comp
uh I'm ready to, you know, compete. Um I
love competing. Um so, you know, uh
honestly, you know, uh I'm just, you
know, eager, you know, uh excited. Um,
I'm ready to get to work.
>> Uh, there was a report that you had like
an east coat in March. Just how you
feeling um, you know, physically and you
think you'll be like ready to go for
>> Yeah. Um, I had an East Co March 12th, I
think about five weeks out. Um, I feel
great. I'm back running. I'm back
running routes. I'm back lifting. So,
you know, um, by the time you know the
rookie mini camp comes, like I'm ready
to go. talked a lot about, you know,
football stuff, but talk about some of
the people that you have that you
brought here and kind of the influence
they played in getting to this point.
>> Yeah, I just brought my my fiance, my
beautiful fiance Sammy. Um, I would have
my parents here, but my brother's in the
draft as well, so they're at home with
him. Um, but just so I'll speak as if my
parents were here as well. Um, uh, they
my both my parents just sacrificed
everything all going up for me to get to
where I'm at today. Um, yeah, there was
no sacrifice too great for them. And
then, uh, her, she's just been the
greatest support of my life. Shoot,
there was, uh, some dog days. Um, some
days that I was real sick during the
season, and she was the one nursing me.
So, um, yeah, I've just had a lot of
incredible support.
>> Yeah. Uh, so above there, I I got my
dad, my mom, you know, um,
my beautiful girlfriend. Um my dad, you
know, um he's the one that, you know, um
he put the football in my hand since,
you know, four years old. Um you know,
uh he just he just, you know, he just,
you know, been, you know, that, you
know, person who, you know, um who
motivates me, who, you know, uh who
pushes me, you know, to my limits. Uh my
mom, you know, um you know, um the
sacrifices, you know, um she had to make
uh you know, uh I got I got, you know,
four little brothers in the house. So,
you know, um so, you know, uh it was so
you know, so you know, just you know,
seeing her, you know, um I sacrificed a
lot, you know, uh it meant a lot. And
you know, uh my girlfriend, you know, um
she has she has been nothing but, you
know, um supportive. Um yeah uh she's
just been you know um the greatest
supporter um a shoulder to lean on and
you know um and an outlet to you know
talk to
>> you talk about the um
I've been watching some of your films
and your route running is obviously one
of your strengths and you're joining
Jerry Judy here uh who is also a great
route runner and prides himself on that.
Have you watched some of Jerry? Have you
watched Jerry film at all to
>> Of course.
>> Talk about him as a route runner and how
you guys might be together in that way.
>> Yeah. Um yeah. Uh of course, you know,
um growing up, you know, uh Alabama, you
know, uh it was a powerhouse. Um just
seeing those guys, you know, uh be
there, you know, um you know, um and
dominate. So, you know, uh once I'm once
I'm finally able to get to, you know, um
meet him, um you know, um and pick his
brain, uh I feel like I feel like me and
his game are going to are going to
compliment are going to complement each
other very very well.
>> There's been a lot said with some of the
new offensive linemen that have come in
this offseason about George Warhop and
kind of what he brings to the table as a
coach. just how much were you able to if
at all interface with him during the
pre-draft process and how excited are
you to to work under him?
>> Um uh I was able to meet him at the at
the combine and on my 30 visit and I
I've it's been awesome. It's been really
awesome to get to know him, meet him. Um
just talking to him, I already know I I
can I already tell what kind of coach he
is. He's definitely an old school an old
school type of coach. Um a very hardcore
type of coach and I that's all I've had.
Um, so I think yeah, that'll be awesome.
>> This is a, you know, lifelong dream for
both of you guys. I'm just curious. When
you were a kid, what part of it did you
dream about? Was it playing? Was it
hearing your name called? What was it?
>> I would say I would say, you know, just
playing honestly. Um, you know, you
know, uh, it really didn't matter, you
know, um,
if I got my name called or not. you
know, uh, you know, uh, you know, uh,
just being able to, you know, um, just
being able to play the game, you know,
that I've that just being able to play
the game that I have loved, you know, as
a kid, honestly.
>> Oh, sorry. I was I was just going to
say, um, I feel like every part of it
has been my dream. Um, hearing my name
called, I mean um, even being here I
feel like has been is a dream to me. uh
getting out to play on Sundays. Um I'm
really grateful because I feel like just
every day I'm out here, I'm in this
league is going to be like I'm living my
dream
>> cuz I am.
>> This question would be for both of you
as well. And that is it's it's not every
year that you have two first round
picks. So I mean have you guys had a
chance to sort of talk to each other a
little bit about how you can be a huge
part of the evolution or the
transformation of offense and kind of uh
Andrew Barry was saying that you know
culture setters and things like that. So
do you feel like you can be uh part of
something big here to get this thing
turned around?
>> Let's do it man.
>> Yeah. Let's do it.
>> Yeah. like uh really really like you
know um
we we really like you know um just met
you know um so you know um just you know
um coming in you know um together um and
just you know um and just you know and
leaning on each other um you know uh
helping each other out you know um and
just you know um and just you know and
and just you know and just establishing
you know
that brotherhood honestly.
>> When you were a kid growing up playing,
did you pretend you're some receiver
like whoever it might be?
>> No. So, uh, actually I I actually grew
up playing a quarterback, honestly. Uh,
I didn't I didn't um I didn't start
playing receiver until my ninth grade
year in uh high school. But I mean, um,
growing up, uh, I used to watch a lot of
Tayvon Austin. Yeah. He, you know, uh,
you know, uh, back then, you know, um,
his, you know, um, his, you know,
college highlights were, you know, were
legendary.
>> Made about your arm length and the whole
draft process. At any time were you
worried that that was gonna
move you down the board or keep you from
playing tackle at this level?
>> No, it's been confusing. We were talking
to someone before. It's like shoot, I
don't even know what my real arm length
is. I mean, uh, we had measured like 32
and 1/8. Uh, freaking proday was
different. Here, when I came out with 30
visit, it was 33. Was it the Steelers?
It was 33. I don't I don't know what
it's like to have 35 inch arms and it
hasn't made too much of a difference.
So,
>> you think that's an overrated aspect
process?
>> I mean, I I feel like I'm sure it has
something to do with it. I mean, I don't
I don't think people would make such a
big deal out of it if it wasn't a thing,
but I don't think anyone has the
athleticism and the feet that I have.
So, I fig in my case, I don't think it
makes a big a big difference.
>> Yesterday, Andrew mentioned too that
they thought that you were the best punt
returner in the class. Just how have you
embraced that part of the game? And are
you looking forward to making waves
here?
>> Oh yes, always. You know, um it's just
you know um it's just it's just you know
it is just it is just another way um how
can you know impact the game. Um you
know um you know um you know uh it
change the game. Um it just it it just
honestly adds on you know to my value.
about the fact that you are joining an
offensive line that's in the middle of a
complete massive overhaul and that
pretty much everybody at every single
position is going to be new and
different. How might that benefit you uh
you know to just kind of be on the
ground floor of a startup line?
>> Um I feel like I don't know it's going
to be exciting. I mean, it's going to be
I'll have a It'll be really fun to have
all of us come time so we can all kind
of build relationships at the same time.
Um, I don't know. It's It's cool not
going into a room where everyone's
already, I don't know, set in stone to
be able to go in a room where we can all
build relationships at the same time.
And I'm excited to be everybody's shadow
um to kind of learn uh how to be great
in this league.
What about the the draft process,
talking to the Browns, meeting with the
Browns, and then being drafted by the
Browns has you excited about the city,
about the the organization? What gets
you excited to be here?
>> I mean, honestly, you know, just, you
know, um the relationships, you know, um
you know, uh everybody, you know, um
everybody, you know, inside the
building, you know, um you know, um from
what I can see is close. um if it feels
like you know um a family environment so
you know uh so you know so you know just
being able to be in that type of
environment.
>> Yeah. And then yeah my two favorite
things so far have been first definitely
the relationships. Um I mean meeting
coach Monkin was so cool. He's such an
awesome he's a great man. Um great
coach. Uh meeting with coach Hob I mean
I'm really I'm so excited to play for
him. And uh my second favorite thing has
actually just been the traffic here. Um
it's been unbelievable. I freaking we
was here at 5:00 p.m. during my freaking
uh my 30 and then there was no there was
nothing. There was nothing. There was
like just straight green lights. So I
was like yeah that was unbelievable.
>> Was there a moment for
>> Was there a moment for either one of you
guys during your visit that you thought,
wow, this could be my landing spot?
Um
I would say I would say probably um
I would say my I would say my my uh walk
through um after you know um we had you
know had you know um our walk through uh
we like you know um
like you know uh
we shot like hoops um you know uh it was
just you know um bonding more, you know,
um
getting getting to getting getting to
know, you know, um each other more. And
and I feel like, you know, uh after
that, you know, it was, you know, I felt
like after that, it was a it was a
strong possibility that if I was there
at at uh 24, I could, you know, become a
a a a Cleveland Brown for sure.
>> Man, I I drove here straight after the
like straight from the combine. and they
drove me here. I feel like that alone I
was like I thought it was pretty cool
and I could see myself being here.
>> The arm length stuff the the one nitpick
on you has been has been the drops. How
do you ease those concerns when someone
brings them up to you? I mean you know
um I just you know uh accepted you know
um you know uh I have I have you know
had you know drops but you know it's
more so you know um
it it is more so you know
concentration um you know uh just you
know focusing on the ball. So you know
um I've been I've been working you know
non-stop at it um every day. So, you
know, um it's gonna get fixed for sure.
>> About stepping into
a quarterback competition. So, both of
you guys are going to be, you know, a
part of that. You probably haven't had a
whole lot of time to think about that
yet, but you know, what do you kind of
know so far a little bit maybe about
Deshawn Watson, Shador Sanders, and you
know, how maybe exciting is it to to see
this whole thing play out?
Well, I mean, just as a lineman, it's um
I'm excited to play for for to play in
front of either of them. I mean, it's so
funny hearing Deshun Watson. It's kind
of like a celebrity name to me. Um but
and then I was able to play against
Shadur in college, too. Uh we we went
101. He beat us uh the last the year
before he left. But um to me, it doesn't
really matter to me. I'll my job is to
block for whoever's back there.
Yeah, I would say, you know, um
both of both both both both both of
those guys, you know, um are legendary.
Um you know, uh honestly, honestly, to
me, you know, um you know, um it doesn't
matter, you know, um
you know, uh it's my job, you know, to
get open, you know, um but you know, um
catch the ball. So, you know, uh whoever
is back there, you know, um I'll just
you
you know, I'll just be, you know, um,
happy for those guys.
>> Oh, this is so tough.
>> What? This is a crazy This is crazy,
>> bro.
Okay, you want to step I can say